so many different
challenges ahead whether it's on the
economic front how about valuations
where do you see the biggest risks
Good morning Sherry morning Hardy I
think that's what we observe is that
there's a lack of risk premium across
most risk asset classes and this also in
certain fixed income asset classes a
lack of term premium as well so we have
to be very very selective and we have to
be wary of allocating risk to parts of
the market where there's an unfavorable
risk reward so what we think is is
important to highlight right now is
there's a lot of rate Cuts priced in in
the U.S treasury market so I think about
65 basis points of cuts in the second
half of this year around 150 basis
points of Great Cuts next year and that
of course is predicated on the
assumption that we will probably enter a
recession and inflatable full quite
precipitously over the coming six
courses or so the question would be what
happens if that doesn't Prevail what
happens if the US economy models through
for at least another six months what
happens if inflation remains stubbornly
High what only Falls at a relatively
modest Pace you would then argue
actually that the front end of the rates
curve does not look particularly
attractive from a risk or perspective
even though at Manulife we do believe
that ultimately we do end up in
recession and recessionary Dynamics do
present themselves probably from the end
of this year onwards
can China provide the much needed upside
when it comes to global economic growth
in when it comes to investment sentiment
as well we just heard that during golden
week Mainland Chinese people were
rushing to Hong Kong to open accounts in
order to start investing
but one thing that we do observe about
China is that the credit impulse is
definitely picking up but the the
ultimate cyclical recovery is starting
to to fade in terms of its power there's
a lot of latent spending potential both
by businesses and households but one
area which has benefited from that
particularly up until now has been
outbound tourism and overseas spending
and that's why you see some of the
luxury Brands listed in Europe the
consumer discretion names performed so
well they've really started to capture
that Revenge spending if you like when
it comes to more domestic spending it's
been a bit of a slower grind higher and
the other point to highlight is because
of the disinflationary and the secular
overhangs of the economy in China more
stimulus is needed but there you see
limited fiscal room for maneuver
particularly by the local government so
it's a bit of a challenging macro
backdrop and on top of that as well
we've got to watch quite carefully with
the regulatory landscape looks like
because it's not the case that the
regulatory risks are now fully behind us
it's just that they're rolling through
different parts of the economy so from
investors perspective we've got to watch
the cost of capital whether it's moving
in the right direction and ultimately
overseas allocators don't like negative
surprises they like continuity and
certainty and visibility when it comes
to policy making